Needed something to do while sick.
Decided on speedrunning.
World record for 120 stars is one hour 40 minutes.
Now, I didn't know how to speedrun, and I haven't played the game in nineteen years,
but I was gonna get a record.
and I did.
So first you want to...
Uhhh.....
I had no idea where I was supposed to go.
I thought it was the castle,
but if I'm wrong,
I'd lose a lot of time.
After timer passed record,
I had two stars.
My entire first attempt took only 80 hours.
Which is pretty fast,
Uh... but not fast enough.
On my second attempt,
I beat the game in half the time.
If I kept t̲h̲i̲s̲ up after 11 attempts, I can beat the game in two minutes!
But that's not what happened.
On my third attempt, I got 39:59.
I needed an edge,
and I found it.
A huge time sink is getting 100 coins for a star.
Solved it by picking up an economics book,
and learned how to deflate currency.
Now I only need 20 coins.
Another trick in the Bowser boss fight you are supposed to throw him against bombs.
You can save a lot of time by bringing bombs from home.
But even with my genius tricks,
I still didn't have enough time.
But then I thought:
"Maybe the problem isn't that I don't have enough time."
Maybe the problem...
is time itself!
So I started studying quantum mechanics to solve time,
and I quickly realized that
it's not making me better at Mario,
and is therefore useless.
Get a real job, you losers!
It was at this point I decided to do the unthinkable...
Learn from other speedrunners.
But they use glitches to get faster
and miss a lot of the game.
Programmers work day and night on this.
If I have to cheat to get the world record,
I don't want it.
No fun in that.
And then it hits me:
people say time flies when you have fun.
So what if I play the game,
while doing my taxes?
Yeah, look how slow one second is now!
One last attempt using all of my newfound knowledge.
I was 40 minutes ahead of other speedruns.
I can do this!
Then the game froze
on my last attempt!
This was no mere coincidence!
This was punishment from
GOOOOODDDUH!!!!
It was only for like a second, so,
it probably was a coincidence.
Yayyy! World Record! I beat the game in one hour!
But it wasn't one hour,
it was a hundred million hours!
The game didn't freeze for one second,
It froze for twelve thousand years!
Which means I have the record for longest play time.
Yaay, Yay!
Oh no, the androids are coming.